Dear 
Craig
 
I have submitted a secure request 
83225510 for an HP OPERATIONS ORCHESTRATOR(HPOO) role OO_ENGINEERING_SERVICES_RUN.
The Username I submitted access for is 
caamodt.
This is so you will be able to submit HPOO reports created for ESD, and currently the FIREWALL TEST OF PORTS report.
 
Instructions on how to access HPOO Central and to run this report, which will help you run future reports also.
 
